Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, circa 1970-2003; Series I; (190 boxes)
  - Exhibition Prints, (73 boxes)
    - 16 inches by 20 inches
      - Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits
        - Constance Cuffee Valdez and Rueben Valdez, 1985 March 2 (Box 41, Folder 914)
        - Rueben Valdez, 1985 March 2 (Box 41, Folder 915)
        - Rueben Valdez and Joshua Cuffee, 1985 March 2 (Box 41, Folder 916)
        - Elizabeth Bess Haile, 1985 March 9 (Box 41, Folder 917)
        - Anthony Crippen, 1985 April 12 (Box 41, Folder 918-919)
        - Rodney Crippen, 1985 April 28 (Box 41, Folder 920)
        - Anita Hearn and Rodney Crippen, 1985 April 28 (Box 41, Folder 921)
        - David Bunn Siklos and Alice Osceola Martinez, 1985 May 22 (Box 41, Folder 922)
        - Michelle Crippen Johnson, 1985 June 5 (Box 42, Folder 923)
        - Kia Gordon, 1985 June 10 (Box 42, Folder 924)
        - Oyster Project; Edward Terry, Mabel Cuffee, and Lamont Smith, 1985 June 18 (Box 42, Folder 925)
        - Meesha Nyeema Johnson, 1985 July 5 (Box 42, Folder 926-927)
        - David Bunn Siklos, 1985 August 2 (Box 42, Folder 928)
        - Karen Smith and Sheron Smith, 1985 August 11 (Box 42, Folder 929)
        - Steven Smith, Karen Smith, and Shavone Smith, 1985 August 12 (Box 42, Folder 930)
        - Tanis Phillips Scott, 1985 September 18 (Box 42, Folder 931)
        - Charles Smith, 1985 October 8 (Box 42, Folder 932)
        - James R. Smith, 1985 October 8 (Box 42, Folder 933)
        - Bernice Smith, 1985 December 3 (Box 42, Folder 934)
        - James Eleazer and Ronald Eleazer, 1986 November 8 (Box 42, Folder 935)
        - Carla Crippen, 1986 November 22 (Box 42, Folder 936)
        - Carla Crippen and John Machiste Audrade, 1986 November 22 (Box 42, Folder 937)
        - Roberta Hunter, 1986 November 22 (Box 42, Folder 938)
        - Roberta Hunter and Glenn Cuyjet, 1986 November 22 (Box 42, Folder 939)
        - Roberta Hunter and Sienna Cuyjet, 1986 November 22 (Box 42, Folder 940)
        - James Kellis, 1987 May 13 (Box 43, Folder 941)
        - Arlene Smith Lincoln, 1987 May 13 (Box 43, Folder 942)
        - James Eleazer, III, 1987 May 21 (Box 43, Folder 943)
        - Valton Reddick, 1987 May 23 (Box 43, Folder 944)
        - Leonard Cuffee, 1987 May 24 (Box 43, Folder 945)
        - Shana Gumbs, 1987 May 24 (Box 43, Folder 946)
        - Ken Thompson, 1987 May 24 (Box 43, Folder 947)
        - Thom Crippen, 1987 May 31 (Box 43, Folder 948)
        - Elizabeth Franklin Goodall, 1987 June 9 (Box 43, Folder 949)
        - Guy Reddick, 1987 June 9 (Box 43, Folder 950)
        - Naike Bess, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 951)
        - Cheryl Terry Franklin and Loretta Terry Reddick, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 952)
        - Ricardo Scott Fleming, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 953)
        - Allison Franklin, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 954)
        - Cheryl Terry Franklin and Allison Franklin, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 955)
        - Tammi Terry, 1987 June 13 (Box 43, Folder 956)
      - Black History & Folklife Project, Riverhead, New York
        - William Hatcher, 1986 February 6 (Box 44, Folder 957)
        - William Hatcher and Annie Hatcher, 1986 February 6 (Box 44, Folder 958)
        - Stewart Harris, 1986 April 11 (Box 44, Folder 959)
        - Pattie Bell, 1986 April 28 (Box 44, Folder 960)
        - Estelle James, 1986 May 7 (Box 44, Folder 961)
        - Lillie Mae Nelson and Carrie Ethel Willis, 1986 May 12 (Box 44, Folder 962)
        - Albert Seay, 1986 May 12 (Box 44, Folder 963)
        - Bessie Gray and Philip Gray, 1986 June 22 (Box 44, Folder 964)
        - Florence Smith, 1986 June 22 (Box 44, Folder 965)
        - Priscilla Brunskill and Florence Smith, 1986 June 22 (Box 44, Folder 966)
        - Betty Harris and her granddaughter, Michelle, 1986 June 22 (Box 44, Folder 967)
        - Joe Michael, Gracie Goodridge, and Lorraine Michelle Michael, 1986 June 29 (Box 44, Folder 968)
        - Ray Mack, 1986 June 29 (Box 44, Folder 969)
        - Gracie Goodridge, 1986 June 29 (Box 44, Folder 970)
        - Cindy Liggon and Brandon Liggon, 1986 June 29 (Box 44, Folder 971)
        - Leroy Anderson and Louise Anderson, 1986 June 29 (Box 44, Folder 972)
        - Shirley Toney, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 973)
        - Yolande Toney, William Toney I, and William Toney II, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 974)
        - Emma Harris, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 975)
        - Reverend Marie Laroche, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 976)
        - Tyrone Trent and Kakesha Minter, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 977)
        - Reverend Hayward Talbert and his daughters, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 978)
        - Nicole Edwards, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 979)
        - Theordore Turpin, 1986 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 980)
        - Tara Stevens, 1986 July 14 (Box 45, Folder 981)
        - Jonathon Ligon, 1986 July 16 (Box 45, Folder 982)
        - Hattie Cook and Octavia Liggens, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 983)
        - Gladys Nelson Baskin, Ruth Henry Baskin, and Mary Henry Darden, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 984)
        - Louise Boyd, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 985)
        - Walter Manley and Elsie Manley, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 986)
        - Hattie Cook, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 987)
        - Larry Brown, 1986 August 3 (Box 45, Folder 988)
      - Heber Springs Portraits
        - Benjamin Johnston, 1989 June 2 (Box 46, Folder 989)
        - Amanda Clark, 1989 August 1 (Box 46, Folder 990)
        - Dorothy Perry, 1990 February 2 (Box 46, Folder 991)
        - Art Gott, 1990 February 2 (Box 46, Folder 992)
        - Arbie Hayes and Homer Hayes, 1990 February 5 (Box 46, Folder 993)
        - Lecil Bishop, 1990 February 7 (Box 46, Folder 994-995)
        - Jean Dunn Kinsey and Carol Dunn Quinn, 1990 February 16 (Box 46, Folder 996)
        - Louie Clark, 1990 February 26 (Box 46, Folder 997)
        - Chris Cuevas, 1990 March 10 (Box 46, Folder 998)
        - Lecil Bishop, 1990 March 21 (Box 46, Folder 999)
        - Guy Hazelwood, 1990 March 22 (Box 46, Folder 1000)
        - Audra Hines Hipp, 1990 March 25 (Box 46, Folder 1001)
        - Art Gott, 1990 March 26 (Box 46, Folder 1002-1003)
        - Dorothy Perry, 1990 March 26 (Box 46, Folder 1004)
        - Clayce Cannon, 1990 April 21 (Box 46, Folder 1005)
        - William Percy Clapp, 1990 April 24 (Box 46, Folder 1006)
        - Mary Albright Clapp, 1990 April 24 (Box 46, Folder 1007)
        - Opal Caley, 1990 April 26 (Box 46, Folder 1008)
        - Louraine Lou Lawson, 1990 April 26 (Box 46, Folder 1009)
        - Donna Lawson Warnick, 1990 April 26 (Box 46, Folder 1010)
        - Lyle Stephenson, 1990 April 28 (Box 46, Folder 1011)
        - Tyrone Phipps, 1990 April 28 (Box 46, Folder 1012)
        - Justin Deckard, 1990 May 5 (Box 47, Folder 1013)
        - Donna Cooke, 1990 May 5 (Box 47, Folder 1014)
        - Mike Eager, 1990 May 5 (Box 47, Folder 1015)
        - Summer Mozeko, 1990 May 5 (Box 47, Folder 1016)
        - Clyde Bittle, 1990 May 8 (Box 47, Folder 1017)
        - Cindy McCord, 1990 May 9 (Box 47, Folder 1018-1019)
        - Cindy McCord and Gail McCord, 1990 May 9 (Box 47, Folder 1020)
        - Tanya Sheley, 1990 May 9 (Box 47, Folder 1021)
        - Todd Spinks, 1990 May 10 (Box 47, Folder 1022)
        - J. C. Verser, 1990 May 12 (Box 47, Folder 1023)
        - Irma Dean Verser, 1990 May 12 (Box 47, Folder 1024)
        - Benjamin Johnston, 1990 May 13 (Box 47, Folder 1025)
        - Estelle "Sissy" Hazelwood, 1990 May 14 (Box 47, Folder 1026)
        - Windle Bittle, 1990 May 14 (Box 47, Folder 1027)
        - Margaret Bittle, 1990 May 19 (Box 47, Folder 1028)
        - Tatum Bittle, 1990 May 19 (Box 47, Folder 1029)
        - Elizabeth Davis and Tammara Davis, 1990 June 1 (Box 47, Folder 1030)
        - Elizabeth Davis, Tammara Davis, and Tiffany Cooper, 1990 June 1 (Box 47, Folder 1031)
        - Tricia Carr Spinks, 1990 June 2 (Box 47, Folder 1032)
        - Julia Chamness Carr, 1990 June 2 (Box 47, Folder 1033)
        - Louise Cook, 1990 June 7 (Box 47, Folder 1034)
        - Henry McMahan, 1990 June 7 (Box 47, Folder 1035)
        - Helen Riggle, 1990 June 7 (Box 47, Folder 1036)
        - Thomas Ivy "Pete" Stark, 1990 June 21 (Box 47, Folder 1037)
        - Ida Bullard Stark, 1990 June 21 (Box 47, Folder 1038)
        - Sylvia Roy, 1990 October 20 (Box 48, Folder 1039)
        - Nancy Bullard Donaldson, 1990 October 20 (Box 48, Folder 1040)
        - Mekay Partridge, 1990 October 21 (Box 48, Folder 1041)
        - Mekay Partridge and Danney Tucker, 1990 October 21 (Box 48, Folder 1042)
        - Geneva Jauch, 1990 October 23 (Box 48, Folder 1043)
        - Harry Neukam, 1990 October 24 (Box 48, Folder 1044)
        - Dudley Lemon, 1990 November 2 (Box 48, Folder 1045)
        - Sam Haile and Steve Haile, 1990 November 8 (Box 48, Folder 1046)
        - Nancy Dayze and Wayne Dayze, II, 1990 November 11 (Box 48, Folder 1047)
        - David Dick, 1990 November 11 (Box 48, Folder 1048)
        - James Dayze, 1990 November 11 (Box 48, Folder 1049)
        - David Dick and Beth Dick, 1990 November 11 (Box 48, Folder 1050)
        - Bynam Bullard, 1990 November 13 (Box 48, Folder 1051)
        - Dorothy Peel Cannon, 1990 November 14 (Box 48, Folder 1052)
        - Victor Lee Presley, 1990 November 17 (Box 48, Folder 1053)
        - Allison Patchell, 1990 November 18 (Box 48, Folder 1054)
        - A. M. "Andy" Killion, E. W. "Elmer" Killion, and C. M. "Clifford" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 48, Folder 1055)
        - A. M. "Andy" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 48, Folder 1056)
        - E. W. "Elmer" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 48, Folder 1057)
        - C. M. "Clifford" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 48, Folder 1058)
        - Benjamin Johnston and Matthew Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 48, Folder 1059-1060)
        - Bill Johnston, Benjamin Johnston, and Matthew Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 48, Folder 1061)
        - B. L. "Bozy" Johnston, Bill Johnston, Benjamin Johnston, and Matthew Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 48, Folder 1062-1063)
        - B. L. "Bozy" Johnston and Bill Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 48, Folder 1064)
        - Carlos Killion, 1991 January 9 (Box 49, Folder 1065)
        - J. A. "Jerry" Moon, 1991 January 18 (Box 49, Folder 1066-1067)
        - Payton Stone, 1991 January 20 (Box 49, Folder 1068-1069)
        - Jenifer Anne Stone, 1991 January 20 (Box 49, Folder 1070)
        - Carl McSpadden, 1991 January 21 (Box 49, Folder 1071)
        - Loy Cannon, 1991 January 22 (Box 49, Folder 1072)
        - Thurmon Bailey, 1991 January 22 (Box 49, Folder 1073)
        - Ruth Faust Hartwick, 1991 January 27 (Box 49, Folder 1074)
        - Mike Haile, Samuel Haile, Jr., and Steve Haile, 1991 Jan 31 (Box 49, Folder 1075)
        - Kenzie Hannah, 1991 January 31 (Box 49, Folder 1076)
        - Michael Provost, 1991 February 2 (Box 49, Folder 1077)
        - Mitchell Stark, 1991 February 5 (Box 49, Folder 1078)
        - Matthew Johnston and Lee Carson, 1991 February 6 (Box 49, Folder 1079)
        - Lee Carson, 1991 February 6 (Box 49, Folder 1080)
        - Everett Henson, 1991 February 13 (Box 49, Folder 1081)
        - Bonnie Kay Buerkle and Christina Belcher, 1991 February 13 (Box 49, Folder 1082)
        - Merrell Stark, 1991 February 17 (Box 49, Folder 1083)
      - Onondaga Nation Portraits
        - Audrey Shenandoah, Jessica Jeanne Shenandoah, and Rochelle Brown, 1991 June 8 (Box 50, Folder 1084)
        - Shenandoah, Jessica Jeanne, and Rochelle Brown, 1991 June 8 (Box 50, Folder 1085)
        - Lewis Farmer, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1086)
        - Betty Jacobs, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1087)
        - Oren R. Lyons, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1088)
        - Alice (Dewasenta) Papineau, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1089)
        - Gerry Papineau, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1090)
        - Norman Powless, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1091)
        - Emerson Waterman, 1991 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 1092)
        - Phoebe Hill, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1093)
        - Keith Printup, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1094-1095)
        - Edward Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1096)
        - Leon Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1097-1098)
        - Leon Shenandoah, Alice (Dewasenta) Papineau, Phoebe Hill, and Edward Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1099)
        - Tracy Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 50, Folder 1100)
        - Alex William Thunder Deer and John Deer, 1991 November 5 (Box 51, Folder 1101)
        - Shannon Booth, 1991 November 7 (Box 51, Folder 1102)
        - Alson Gibson and Diane E. Gibson, 1991 November 10 (Box 51, Folder 1103)
        - New longhouse, 1991 December 14 (Box 51, Folder 1104)
        - Jada Hopper, 1991 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 1105)
        - Sherri L. Waterman-Hopper, 1991 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 1106)
        - Alicia A. Cook, 1992 February 16 (Box 51, Folder 1107)
        - Brenda Cook, 1992 February 17 (Box 51, Folder 1108)
        - Boo Crouse, 1992 February 17 (Box 51, Folder 1109)
        - Boo Crouse and Brenda Cook, 1992 February 17 (Box 51, Folder 1110)
        - Ambrose Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1111)
        - Diane Gibson and Missy Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1112)
        - Missy Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1113)
        - Teresa Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1114)
        - Mary Honyoust, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1115)
        - P. Wade Printup, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1116-1117)
        - Edward Shenandoah, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1118)
        - Edward Shenandoah, Allen Shenandoah, Robert Shenandoah, and Keith Shenandoah with snow snakes, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1119)
        - Edward Shenandoah with snow snakes, 1992 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 1120)
        - Johnson H. John, 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1121)
        - Johnson H. John and Taylor A. John, 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1122)
        - Barry Powless, 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1123-1124)
        - Irving Powless, Jr., 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1125-1129)
        - Irving Powless, Jr., and Barry Powless, 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1130)
        - Laureen Powless, 1992 February 19 (Box 52, Folder 1131)
        - Maxine Crouse, 1992 February 20 (Box 53, Folder 1132-1133)
        - Leslie Powless, 1992 February 20 (Box 53, Folder 1134)
        - Elizabeth Rockwell, 1992 February 20 (Box 53, Folder 1135)
        - Joshua Rockwell, 1992 February 20 (Box 53, Folder 1136)
        - Helen M. Casey, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1137)
        - Angus Cook, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1138-1139)
        - Cora Gibson Elm, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1140)
        - Verna Jones and Courtney Lazore, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1141)
        - Spencer Lyons and Maria Lyons, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1142)
        - Adam Printup, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1143)
        - Alma A. Printup, 1992 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 1144)
        - Regina Jones, 1992 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 1145)
        - Regina Jones, Keith Shenandoah, Sunny Shenandoah, Cassie Shenandoah, Lynn Shenandoah, and Helen Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 1146)
        - Regina Jones, Sunny Shenandoah, Cassie Shenandoah, Lynn Shenandoah, and Helen Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 1147)
        - Keith Shenandoah, Sunny Shenandoah, Cassie Shenandoah, Lynn Shenandoah, and Helen Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 1148)
        - Sunny Shenandoah and Cassie Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 1149)
        - First Methodist Church, 1992 April 23 (Box 53, Folder 1150)
        - Home and property of Lewis Farmer, 1992 April 23 (Box 53, Folder 1151-1152)
        - Seventh Day Adventist Church, 1992 April 23 (Box 53, Folder 1153)
        - Wade Allen Cook, 1992 April 24 (Box 54, Folder 1154)
        - Marion Green and Mary Honyoust, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1155)
        - Summer Honyoust, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1156)
        - Jesse Jacobs, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1157)
        - Ira Osciola Johnson, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1158)
        - Eulalie Moses, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1159)
        - Percy Shenandoah, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1160)
        - Percy Shenandoah and Edward Shenandoah, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1161)
        - Sharon Shenandoah, Percy Shenandoah, Edward Shenandoah, and Wade A. Cook, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1162)
        - Esther Sullivan, Dale Solomon, and Rosetta McClairy, 1992 April 25 (Box 54, Folder 1163)
        - Sidney I. Hill, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1164)
        - Emma Shenandoah, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1165)
        - Emma Shenandoah and Skasenito Shenandoah, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1166)
        - Jessica Shenandoah and Alicia Shenandoah, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1167)
        - Skasenito Shenandoah, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1168)
        - Tracy Shenandoah, Sam Shenandoah, Emma Shenandoah, Jessica Shenandoah, Alicia Shenandoah, Skasenito Shenandoah, and Lena Shenandoah, 1992 April 26 (Box 54, Folder 1169)
        - Jacqueline A. Coulan, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1170)
        - Bertha Dimmler, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1171)
        - Bertha Dimmler and Jacqueline A. Coulan, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1172)
        - Victoria Isaac, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1173)
        - Warren Isaac, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1174)
        - Doris Lewis, 1992 June 23 (Box 55, Folder 1175)
        - Onondaga Nation School, 1992 June 24 (Box 55, Folder 1176)
        - Onondaga Nation School, Graduating Class, 1992 June 25 (Box 55, Folder 1177)
        - Buffalo, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1178)
        - Lloyd M. Elm, Jr., 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1179)
        - Paul Elm, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1180)
        - Amy M. Gibson, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1181)
        - Handsome Lake Marker, Old Shenandoah House, Old Longhouse, and New Longhouse, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1182)
        - Jeanette Lowe, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1183)
        - Lee M. Anderson Lyons, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1184)
        - Lee M. Anderson Lyons and Susan Lyons, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1185)
        - Kingsley D. Lyons, Jr., and Dean Addison Lyons, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1186)
        - New longhouse, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1187)
        - Paul Shenandoah, Adah Shenandoah, and Pete Shenandoah, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1188)
        - Paul Shenandoah, Amy M. Gibson, Percy Shenandoah, Edward Shenandoah, Scheen Shenandoah, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1189)
        - Paul Shenandoah and Amy M. Gibson, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1190)
        - Sacheen Shenandoah, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1191)
        - Studio in the old longhouse, 1992 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 1192-1193)
        - Alson John Gibson, Wewoka Shenandoah, and Neal Powless, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1194-1195)
        - David Honyoust and Leon Stout, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1196)
        - Neal Powless, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1197)
        - Charmaine Smith, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1198)
        - Allison Crouse, Aaron Crouse, and Samantha Moses, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1199)
        - Episcopal Church of the Good Shepard, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1200)
        - Eulalie Moses, Allison Crouse, and Samantha Moses, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1201)
        - Robert Moses and Samantha Moses, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1202)
        - Audrey Shenandoah, Courtney Lazore, and Rachel Lazore, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1203)
        - Audrey Shenandoah, Jessica Jeanne Shenandoah, Verna Jones, and Courtney Lazore, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1204)
        - Tianausdi Shenandoah, S'hahaeyjē Shenandoah, and Wewoka Shenandoah, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1205)
        - Wewoka Shenandoah, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1206)
        - Edward Skye, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1207)
        - Geraldine Steeprock, Vincent Steeprock, and Lydia Bea Thomas, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1208)
        - Peggy Steeprock, Julian Steeprock, and Jordan Steeprock, 1992 July 27 (Box 56, Folder 1209)
      - Onondaga Nation Portraits - Prints for Book
        This grouping of exhibition prints were printed by Tucker for her book, Haudenosaunee: Portraits of the Firekeepers, the Onondaga Nation
        - Betty Jacobs, 1991 June 13 (Box 57, Folder 1210)
        - Norman Powless, 1991 June 13 (Box 57, Folder 1211)
        - Emerson Waterman, 1991 June 13 (Box 57, Folder 1212)
        - Phoebe Hill, 1991 September 15 (Box 57, Folder 1213)
        - Edward Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 57, Folder 1214)
        - Leon Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 57, Folder 1215)
        - Leon Shenandoah, Alice (Dewasenta) Papineau, Phoebe Hill, and Edward Shenandoah, 1991 September 15 (Box 57, Folder 1216)
        - Alex William Thunder Deer and John Deer, 1991 November 5 (Box 57, Folder 1217)
        - Shannon Booth, 1991 November 7 (Box 57, Folder 1218)
        - Alson Gibson, 1991 November 10 (Box 57, Folder 1219)
        - Old longhouse, 1991 December 14 (Box 57, Folder 1220-1221)
        - Charles J. Honyoust, 1991 December 15 (Box 57, Folder 1222)
        - Alicia A. Cook, 1992 February 16 (Box 57, Folder 1223)
        - Boo Crouse, 1992 February 17 (Box 57, Folder 1224)
        - Alson John Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 57, Folder 1225)
        - Missy Gibson, 1992 February 18 (Box 57, Folder 1226)
        - Mary Honyoust, 1992 February 18 (Box 57, Folder 1227)
        - Edward Shenandoah, Allen Shenandoah, Robert Shenandoah, and Keith Shenandoah, with snow snakes, 1992 February 18 (Box 57, Folder 1228)
        - Keith Shenandoah, 1992 February 18 (Box 57, Folder 1229)
        - Barry Powless, 1992 February 19 (Box 57, Folder 1230)
        - Leslie Powless, 1992 February 20 (Box 57, Folder 1231)
        - Joshua Rockwell, 1992 February 20 (Box 57, Folder 1232)
        - Helen M. Casey, 1992 February 21 (Box 57, Folder 1233)
        - Angus Cook, 1992 February 21 (Box 57, Folder 1234)
        - Spencer Lyons and Maria Lyons, 1992 February 21 (Box 57, Folder 1235)
        - Alma A. Printup, 1992 February 21 (Box 57, Folder 1236)
        - Regina Jones, Sunny Shenandoah, Cassie Shenandoah, Lynn Shenandoah, and Helen Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 57, Folder 1237)
        - Keith Shenandoah, Sunny Shenandoah, Cassie Shenandoah, Lynn Shenandoah, and Helen Shenandoah, 1992 February 22 (Box 57, Folder 1238)
        - Marion Green and Mary Honyoust, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1239)
        - Summer Honyoust, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1240)
        - Jesse Jacobs, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1241)
        - Ira Osciola Johnson, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1242)
        - Eulalie Moses, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1243)
        - Sharon Shenandoah, Percy Shenandoah, Edward Shenandoah, and Wade A. Cook, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1244)
        - Esther Sullivan, Dale Solomon, and Rosetta McClairy, 1992 April 25 (Box 58, Folder 1245)
        - Bertha Dimmler and Jacqueline A. Coulan, 1992 June 23 (Box 58, Folder 1246)
        - Victoria Isaac, 1992 June 23 (Box 58, Folder 1247)
        - Doris Lewis, 1992 June 23 (Box 58, Folder 1248)
        - Onondaga Nation School, Graduating Class, 1992 June 25 (Box 58, Folder 1249)
        - Paul Elm, 1992 June 26 (Box 58, Folder 1250)
        - Jeanette Lowe, 1992 June 26 (Box 58, Folder 1251)
        - Lee M. Anderson Lyons and Susan Lyons, 1992 June 26 (Box 58, Folder 1252)
        - Kingsley D. Lyons, Jr., and Dean Addison Lyons, 1992 June 26 (Box 58, Folder 1253)
        - New longhouse, 1992 June 26 (Box 58, Folder 1254)